A Guide to the Omicron Delta Kappa, University of Virginia, General Records, 1948-1984
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Omicron Delta Kappa, University of Virginia, General Records 1948-1984
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
RG-24/17/1.841, RG-24/17/1.861
This collection consists of 9 boxes.
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
There are no restrictions.
Acquisition Information
RG-24/17/1.841 was a gift; RG-24/17/1.861 was transferred; and RG-24/17/1.901 was also a gift.
Scope and Content
Records of the University of Virginia Chapter of the Omicron Delta Kappa leadership honorary society, including minutes, correspondence, treasurer's records, financial reports, election records, and membership lists.
Contents List
- Activities and Administration Resource File n.d. (Box 1)
- Correspondence 1968-1973, 6 folders (Box 1)
- Correspondence 1974-1981, 8 folders (Box 2)
- Correspondence 1981-1983, 2 folders (Box 3)
- Elections 1968-1974 Apr, 6 folders (Box 3)
- Elections 1974 Dec-1979 Apr, 6 folders (Box 4)
- Elections 1979 Oct-1984 Mar, 8 folders (Box 5)
- Final Report of Arthur F. Stocker 1984 (Box 5)
- Hollins Inauguration of Paula P. Brownlee 1982 (Box 5)
- Lists--Membership [RG-24/17/1.901] [1962] (Box 5)
- Lists--Officers and Members [RG-24/17/1.901] [1967-1968] (Box 5)
- Lists of Initiates (1925-1973) n.d. (Box 5)
- Mailing Lists (superseded) 1972-1975 (Box 6)
- Mailing Lists 1976-1984, 3 folders (Box 6)
- Memoranda 1968-1981 (Box 6)
- Minutes of the Virginia Circle 1970, 1979-1982 (Box 6)
- Miscellaneous Material 1979-1980 (Box 6)
- National Convention 1970-1972 (Box 6)
- Nomination Committee--Instructions [RG-24/17/1.901] [1965-1966] (Box 6)
- Recommendations for Membership 1978-1978 (Box 7)
- Rituals and Extracts for Initiation 1965, n.d. (Box 7)
- Shannon Award of the Laurel Crowned Circle Award, with 1980 May-Dec (Box 7)
- Treasurers Reports 1968-1983, 3 folders (Box 7)
- Account Books 1948-1982, 2 volumes (Box 7)
- Printed Materials 1965-1984 (Box 7)
- Petitions for Establishing New Chapters 1968-1972 (Box 8)
- Banner of the Omicron Delta Kappa Honor Society n.d. (Box 8)
- Minute Book 1975-1984 (Box 8)
- Minute Book 1961-1975 (Box 9)